<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kid Safe Mode</string>
    <string name="sms_text_header">Register a Keyword and a set of Actions from below list. Whenever a message with registered Keyword is received from any of the parents mobile number, all the actions registered with that keyword will be executed</string>
    <string name="settings_sub_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="sms_actions">Sms Actions</string>
    <string name="timer_actions">Timer Actions</string>
    <string name="contacts_title">Contacts</string>
    <string name="permissions_title">Permissions</string>
    <string name="locktext"><b>Lock</b> - Screen will be Locked when a message \'Lock\' is received</string>
    <string name="kidmodetext"><b>Kidmode</b> - Selected settings in Sms Actions will be done when a message \'Kidmode\' is received</string>
    <string name="smspolicytext"><i>Click here to read Sms Policy</i></string>
    <string name="smsactionsheader"><i><b>Note:</b> Sms messages will be considered only from Registered Mobile Numbers. Click here to Add/Update</i></string>
    <string name="PermissionsRequired"><b>Permissions Required</b></string>
    <string name="ContactsRequired"><b>Register Contacts</b></string>
    <string name="sharingIntentText">Kid Safe Mode(Parental Control)\n\n
                                     Do you want to keep your Infants and Toddlers safe from the Smart Phones?\n
                                     Do you want to make them leave the Smart Phones without making them cry ?\n
                                     Tryout this Free application></string>
    <string name="SmspolicyTextHeader">Sms Policy</string>
    <string name="SmsPolicy">
        1. Sms messages will be read only when Receive and Read Sms Permission is given by the user\n\n
        2. Only Sms messages received from registered mobile number(s) will be read\n   All other messages will be ignored\n\n
        3. Sms Actions will work only if the message content is equal to "Lock" or "Kidmode"(both are case-insensitive). All other messages will be ignored\n\n
        4. Sms messages are not stored anywhere. No message is sent to the cloud (This app doesn\'t have internet access)\n\n
        5. Screen Lock will happen only when Lock Action is enabled in "Sms Actions"\n   Enabling it requires ReadSms and Device Admin Permission to Lock the Screen\n\n
        6. Screen Lock will happen when an Sms \'Lock\'(case-insensitive) is received from any of the registered mobile numbers.\n\n      Screen Lock will happen 10 seconds after receiving the Sms\n\n
        7. Kid Safe Mode Settings will be executed only when it is enabled in "Sms Actions"\n   Enabling it requires ReadSms Permission\n\n
        8. Kid Safe Mode settings will be executed only when an Sms \'kidmode\'(case-insensitive) is received from any of the registered mobile numbers.\n\n    Kid Safe Mode settings will be executed 10 seconds after receiving the Sms\n\n
        9. Additional \'Modify System Settins\' permission is required to enable \'Turn Off Screen\' and \'Brightness\' options\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="TurnOffScreen">Turn Off Screen</string>
    <string name="MinimizeAllApps">Minimize All Apps</string>
    <string name="LockTheScreen">Lock the Screen</string>
    <string name="TurnOffWifi">Turn Off Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="TurnOnSilentMode">Turn On Silent Mode</string>
    <string name="MediaVolume">Media Volume</string>
    <string name="Brightness">Brightness</string>
    <string name="Rating">Give Rating</string>
    <string name="RatingText">*This app is for a Good Cause. Please give your rating</string>
</resources>
